me
The theme is 4Paris Pirates: Midsummer's Grand Reveal.
I wanted to do something like a concept live show, you know, a little bit like a play with pots and pans in between.
I wanted to do a song with dialogue parts.
I wanted to change the image of the costume.
I wanted to change the costume from a pirate-like costume to a cute adult-like costume.
I didn't have color pencils, but I had some, and this is the first pirate, red and black, and this is the second pirate, red and black.
I don't know if I'll be able to do this in black, but ideally...
I don't know if I can do it in black, but ideally, I'd like it to be like a black woutera, with black washi paper that can be removed and become a denim skirt, maybe.
I'd like to wear it with a lot of gusto.
I want to wear an outfit like a sparkling idol.
It's so short.
I guess a mini-skirt would be fine. Yes, I'll wear a mini-skirt.
Even though I drew this picture...
I knew the lines didn't mean anything.
I drew today's picture, the first one.
Which one? I was like, “What are you drawing?” There was a trashy one.
The picture is totally convincing.
The lowest is the moon. Tsuki told me.
What? That I'm not good at it.
If we'd shown each other our drawings, then they'd be in black and white.
Yes, sir.
Thank you.
You're so cute. Thank you.
No, it's not...
So cute!
It's so cute. Thank you.
It's perfect.
Can you do something stylish like this for me? Oh, wow.
Wow. Thank you so much.
It's delicious. It's going to change a lot.
Can you draw it?
If I get one like this, I'll want to wear it.
Well, you can wear it.
You're right. You'll wear it.
That's for sure.
Thank you very much.
Can't I change out of this yet? Can't I change out of these yet?
No, let's put it on.
Let's see, guys. Is it okay if I wear a skirt?
Yeah, this way.
It's so cute. It's so cute.
It's like a belt, but it looks like a sailor suit.
I have another idea.
I made it so you can wear it on top.
To change into something totally different? Yeah.
That's amazing!
You're an idol! You're an idol!
Oh, my God.
The line where you can see her belly.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
So that you can see the locks.
It's perfect, isn't it?
Perfect.
I'm like...
It's kind of sparkly, girlie.
Like the kind of idol that girls like.
I like that.
I've been an idol for a long time.
I've always admired idols because they're so different from me.
I'm glad to hear that, because I've always wanted to be an idol.
I'm glad to hear that.
Thank you very much.
Pain.
Failure
после is
Great ус
Failure
Great This bitch
encounters
ko
Thank you very much.
Halloween donkey's.
I can't take it if I'm next to you. You can't take it with me next to you.
No, I thought.
Thank you very much.
How's it going?
I'm kind of in the middle of a costume change.
At my last fitting...
I was fitted for the costume after the transformation first.
This is the first time I'm wearing the pirate costume.
This is the first time I've worn this pirate costume.
This is the costume after the change.
This one is fine, too.
It's all right.
The inside of this pirate costume is the same as the one I'm wearing in the sale.
So I was able to change very quickly.
It's like this.
I don't know...
It looks like a totally different costume, doesn't it?
but with all these layers on top of each other
I'm not sure if it's my own
I'm not very good at drawing...
I can't believe that a rough sketch of mine
I was so happy to see how you made it into such a wonderful costume.
I was really happy.
The pirate look is amazing, isn't it?
It's amazing, isn't it?
The face is so dirty too!
Soooo...
After the battle
I had him put it in.
It's so amazing, isn't it?
I made two kinds of costumes for this show.
One is my favorite sparkling and idol-like costume, and the other is my favorite sparkling and idol-like costume.
And the other one
I have the impression that playboys like costumes with a fixed concept.
I have the impression that playmates like things that have a solid concept.
I thought it would appeal to them.
I made this pirate costume to appeal to playboys.
I tried on a pirate costume for Gampery. I put on a pirate costume for the Gampery.
Yes, sir.
I feel like a pirate.
I think the pirate gang looks great on him.
I'm sure you'll be able to enjoy both the cute and cool looks of Oshimen.
I'm sure you'll be able to enjoy both of them at once at the show.
Please vote for me, Aina Stan!
Yes, please vote for me, Aina Stan!
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Yes, please vote for me!
Yes, please vote for me.
Yes, sir.
Yes. Yes.